rankpay.com 2013-06-06

# Privacy Policy | RankPay

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you sign up for SEO services. When ordering/registering on our site, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, phone number and credit card information as appropriately as possible. You may, however, visit our site anonymously at any time.

Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * **To personalize your experience** (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * **To improve our website** (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * **To send periodic emails**  
Customer will not receive any continual email solicitation from the company, unless the customer consents to the solicitation at checkout, or through a double opt-in process. And, if the customer does consent to receive email from the company, the company agrees to have a simple unsubscribe option available, along with unsubscribe instructions in every email.  

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order.

After a transaction, your private information (credit card number, billing address, etc.) will be kept on file for more than 60 days in order to appropriately charge for RankPay services..

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.  

## Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.rankpay.com/tos>.  

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.  

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

The RankPay Company   
3052 Clairemont Drive Suite B  
San Diego, CA 92117  
USA  
messages@rankpay.com  
877-RANK-PAY
